We have to work hard for our studio's survival.
生き残るため
Let's wrap up this meeting.
会議はここまで
I'll send everyone the script a little later.
後でみんなに台本を共有する
All right. I want to ask each of you to make sure you take care of your own preparation work.
よろしく頼むぞ
Thank you for your hard work.
お疲れ様
Hey, Rosie Lin, come sit down for a minute.
リンシャン
I have something I want to talk to you about.
話したいことがあるんだ
Take a look.
見てください
Hey, when your at work you should be working.
仕事中じゃないのか？
Why are you shooting & filming this?
何やってるんだ
That's crazy.
ダメじゃないか
How am I being crazy?
そんなことないですよ
I don't have any work right now!
仕事してないわけじゃないですよ
Let me tell you something.
あの
I still have the nude pics on my cell phone.
服着てないバージョンもありますよ
Do you want to see it?
見ますか？
No…No…No
いや、大丈夫だ
Stop making a scene! Don't make a scene.
そんなことしなくていい
You're such a pervert!
ホントに変態だな
Come on, it's not that bad.
普通ですよ
Well, even if someone else wanted to see it, they can't.
誰にでも見せるわけじゃないですよ
Oh!
そうか
I have something I want to talk to you about that is very important.
真面目に話したいことがあるんだ
I have some works for you to do.
仕事を振ろうと思って
Come here and check out this project.
これを見てくれ
Well, our new project is a little more complicated this time around.
今回の企画はちょっと複雑なんだ
And that you are also in charge of the cosplayer's roles for the project.
ここのコスプレ部分をお願いしたい
Then you have to get me a set of sexy lingerie.
一着セクシーな下着を用意して欲しい
Ok, done, no problem.
問題ありません
Let me tell you. I 'm really good at picking out lingerie.
私、こうゆうの得意なんです
Well, in that case.
じゃあ
Do you want to go shopping with me after work?
仕事終わり一緒に買いに行きますか？
Huh? Why would I go shopping with you?
何で一緒に行くんだ
Ah….Please!
お願いしますよ
All right.
分かったよ
We'll talk after work.
仕事が終わってからまた話そう
Yes, you are the best!
やったー！優しいですね
See you after work.
じゃあ、仕事終わりに
So, it's a date.
デートですね
You pinky promise!
約束ですよ
OK. Ok
はいはい
Love you.
愛してまーす
I really can't stand you.
しょうがないな
Ugh, I can't stand you.
ホントしょうがないやつだな
Ugh. What are you doing?
どうです？
Do you like the way my skirt looks?
スカート可愛いですよね？
It's too short.
短すぎ
Your ass is hanging out for everyone to see.
お尻が見えちゃうよ
It's not that bad. You are such an old fart!
オジさんみたいなこと言わないでください
Okay, it's fine.
いや何でもない
Forget about it.
なかったことにしてくれ
So, we are here
着いたから
I'm going to wait for you out front.
外で待ってるぞ
What? You're not coming in with me?
一緒に行くんじゃないんですか？
No, I don't want to go in.
大丈夫
I'll just wait for you here.
ここで待ってるから
Aww, come on, come on.
来てください
Come on, lets go in together.
一緒に行きましょうよ
Mmn…OK.
分かった
Don't worry.
心配しないでください
Come on, let's go!
早く行きましょう
Come.
早く
Wow, look that!
これ見てください
Look at that. It has really big boobs.
めっちゃおっぱい大きいです
It Looks like they feel really nice to touch.
揉み心地よさそう
It looks so bouncy & fun.
ハリがあります
I really want to grab them.
揉んでみたいです
They really are very pretty.
確かにキレイだな
Yes they are!
はい
It's skin is better than mine.
肌も私よりいいかも
Sigh
これ
I've got the exact same one.
私も同じの持ってます
Let me tell you something.
言いたいことがあるんですよ
Come on let me tell you a little secret.
実はですね
I use it every morning.
毎朝いつも使ってるんですよ
Huh?
え？
So is that why you're always late in the morning.
だから、朝遅刻してるのか
I'm not telling you.
教えてあげません
That's so cool.
すごいな
What is this?
何これ？
Take a look at this one. It goes up and down.
上下に動いてますよ
Yep, it's looks pretty awesome.
これはすごいな
It looks really cool.
すごいですよね
So cool
本当すごい
There's so much amazing stuff.
見たことない物が沢山あります
Wow. It looks like you're in paradise.
君が好きなものじゃない？
Holy cow there is so many!
沢山あります
Look at this lingerie.
見てみますね
This one looks amazing.
これ良さそう
Take a look.
見てください
Can I try it on?
開けて良いのか？
I'm sorry but no, you can open it to take a closer look at it.
試着してみないと
Wow, look
どうですか？
This one is great.
良いですよね
Yes, it looks good.
確かに良い感じだな
Yep, I think it'll look really nice on me.
私に似合うと思います
Let me look at another one.
他のも見てみますね
This one kind of looks like a nurse's outfit.
看護師みたいだな
Yes they are!
ですね
Which one do you like?
どっちが良いですかね
Can I get both of them?
どっちも買った方が良いですかね
Sure why not!
いいかも
Then I'll buy it and wear it for you to look at.
帰ってから着て見せますね
Sure.
いいよ
Pay for it.
会計しないと
Let's go.
行きましょう
Senior classmate, does this lingerie look good on me?
學長好看嗎